greetingcarduniverse.com 2018-06-30

# Privacy Policy - member & reminder information never compromised

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for GreetingCardUniverse.com, owned by BigDates.com Inc. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personally identifiable information and how you can access and update this information. 

GreetingCardUniverse.com is commited to your privacy and is determined to respect your trust and confidence. At GreetingCardUniverse.com we agree to notify you of: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site 
  * The organization collecting the information 
  * How the information is used 
  * With whom the information may be shared 
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information 
  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under GreetingCardUniverse.com control 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, please contact [ privacy@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:privacy@greetingcarduniverse.com). 

Under the EU General Data Protection Regulation 2016/679 (GDPR) you have a number of rights you can exercise over your data. Your rights are to: 

  * Receive a copy of your data free of charge 
  * Receive certain data in an electronic format that can be given to another provider 
  * Have data corrected if it is inaccurate 
  * Ask us to stop processing or object to processing under certain circumstances 
  * Ask us to erase data in certain circumstances 
  * Withdraw consent at any time when that is the legal basis for our processing 

Please contact [ security@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:security@greetingcarduniverse.com) for any details. 

GreetingCardUniverse.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. GreetingCardUniverse.com collects information from our users at several different points on our website. 

In order to use this website, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give their contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to contact the user about the services on our site for which they have expressed interest. It is optional for the user to provide billing information (such as credit card number), and other information (such as interests and hobbies), but encouraged so we can provide a more efficient and personalized experience on our site. 

We request information from the user on our order form. Here a user may provide recipient contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. 

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by Greeting Card Universe.com and our partners, affiliates, or analytics or service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis. 

We use cookies for our shopping cart, to remember users' settings such as currency and card personalization. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited. 

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. 

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, or site functionality. 

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by [ clicking here](https://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads. 

We may share or sell 

_aggregated_

(not personally identifiable) demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is NOT linked to any personally identifiable information. 

We may use an outside shipping company to ship orders, and a credit card processing company to bill users for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes and are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us. 

We may partner with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. For example a Greeting Card printer will need a Return & ShipTo address to fulfill an order. 

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personally identifiable information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. If GreetingCardUniverse.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personally identifiable information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personally identifiable information, to any other third party with your prior consent to do so. 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we at Greeting Card Universe are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button [and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site]. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

If a user wishes to subscribe to our email reminders or phone reminders, we ask for contact information such as name, email address, and cell phone email address. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our email or phone reminders by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email and phone preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at [ support@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:support@greetingcarduniverse.com). 

Information such as interest, hobbies, and other attributes both from and member and their recipients play a vital role for the recommendation engine to offer tailored suggestions of goods and services. This information is completely optional and is required only if the member desires specifically tailored suggestions of greeting cards, gifts, and other goods and services. 

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [ testimonials@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:testimonials@greetingcarduniverse.com). 

Our Web site offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personally identifiable information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [ privacy@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:privacy@greetingcarduniverse.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personally identifiable information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why. 

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask for the friend's name and email address. GreetingCardUniverse.com will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit and join the site. GreetingCardUniverse.com will not use this information to send promotional emails. 

Your friend may contact us at [ support@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:support@greetingcarduniverse.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

This website takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. 

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry \- Transport Layer Security (TLS). While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on Web browsers such as Firefox, Chrome and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing. 

While we use TLS encryption encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to your information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Every quarter, as well as any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. Finally, the servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. Click here to verify our [ Secured Site Certification](https://seal.godaddy.com/verifySeal?sealID=XIJhkVBp5CCqRGEJk9RmDw3L35bTpWzDnKMICIVX1BS1PSz97vZkP). 

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [ security@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:security@greetingcarduniverse.com). 

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and special deals. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications by updating  My Privacy Preferences options. 

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We communicate with the user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account via email or phone. 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personally identifiable information provided to us. This can usually be done by emailing our Customer Support at [ support@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:support@greetingcarduniverse.com), or by contacting us at 877-347-6784. 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-in' and 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes directly and indirectly related to our site like periodic updates on special promotions, communications directly with user "recipients" and the sharing or sale of non-personally identifiable information to third parties. Users can easily update their privacy preference options at any time in  My Privacy Preferences My Privacy Preferences. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line to [ unsubscribe@greetingcarduniverse.com](mailto:unsubscribe@greetingcarduniverse.com) or by simply updating their My Privacy Preferences options. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email prior to the change becoming effective. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

If you have any questions or need more information regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

GreetingCardUniverse.com   
154 East Prospect Avenue, Suite B   
Danville, CA 94526   
Phone#: 877-347-6784
